Guide to the Trinity College of Arts and Sciences, Office of the Dean records, 1911-2006 UA.25.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Container List
  - Career Development, 1987-1989 (Box 110)
  - Center for Health Policy, Research and Education, 1982-1984 (Box 110)
  - Chairmen, Arts and Sciences, 1986-1989 (Box 110)
  - Chairmen's Council, 1985-1989 (Box 110)
  - Chancellor of the University, 1987-1989 (Box 110)
  - Chemistry 11 and 12, 1985 (Box 110)
  - Chemistry Department, 1987-1989 (Box 110)
  - Chemistry Department, 1985-1986 (Box 111)
  - Child Care, University Task Force on, 1988-1989 (Box 111)
  - China Exchange Program, 1985-1988 (Box 111)
  - Chronicle of Higher Education, 1982-1984 (Box 111)
  - Class Directory, 1986 (Box 111)
  - Classical Studies Department, 1986-1989 (Box 111)
  - College Board, 1986-1988 (Box 111)
  - College USA, 1986 (Box 111)
  - COLOE Administration, 1985-1986 (Box 111)
  - COLOE Proposals, 1984-1985 (Box 111)
  - Commencement, 1986-1989 (Box 111)
  - Committee on Facilities and Environmental Concerns, 1986 (Box 111)
  - Commonwealth Fund, 1987 (Box 111)
  - Comparative Area Studies, 1985-1988 (Box 111)
  - Comparative Literature, 1986-1988 (Box 111)
  - Computer Science Department, 1989 (Box 111)
  - Computer Science Department, 1985-1988 (Box 112)
  - Computer Science-NSF CER Proposal, 1983-1985 (Box 112)
  - Computer Science-NSF Proposal, 1980-1983 (Box 112)
  - Computer Science-NSF, 1980-1981 (Box 112)
  - Computer Science Review, 1982-1983 (Box 112)
  - Computing, Ad Hoc Committee on, Undergraduate, 1985-1987 (Box 112)
  - Consortium of Social Science Associations, 1984-1989 (Box 112)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, COFHE, 1987-1989 (Box 112)
  - Continuing Education, 1987-1990 (Box 112)
  - Continuing Education, 1985-1986 (Box 113)
  - Coordinate Teaching Across School Boundaries (Box 113)
  - Counseling Night, 1985-1986 (Box 113)
  - Course Schedules, 1987-1989 (Box 113)
  - Dana Wards, Charles A., 1986 (Box 113)
  - Dana Foundation, Charles A. Minority Initiative, 1988 (Box 113)
  - Dance Program, 1981-1989 (Box 113)
  - Deane Gift, 1986-1987 (Box 113)
  - Dean's Arts Advisory Council, 1987-1988 (Box 113)
  - Dean's Club, 1985-1986 (Box 113)
  - Deans Conference, 1987-1989 (Box 113)
  - Deans Council, 1989 (Box 113)
  - Deans Council, 1985-1989 (Box 114)
  - Deans Staff, 1987-1989 (Box 114)
  - Deans Staff Minutes and Agenda, 1983-1989 (Box 114)
  - Demographic Studies, 1987-1989 (Box 114)
  - Development, 1986-1989 (Box 115)
  - Directors of Graduate Studies, 1987-1989 (Box 115)
  - Directors of Undergraduate Studies, 1986-1989 (Box 115)
  - Directory, Academic, 1981-1987 (Box 115)
  - Distinguished Professors, 1987-1989 (Box 115)
  - Distinguished Professors, Seminars, 1986-1989 (Box 115)
  - Distinguished Professors Seminars and Senior Women Nomination, 1985-1986 (Box 115)
  - Divinity School, 1987-1989 (Box 115)
  - Divinity School, 1986 (Box 116)
  - Documentary Studies, 1987-1988 (Box 116)
  - Drama, 1986-1989 (Box 116)
  - Drama Planning, 1986-1987 (Box 116)
  - Duke Annual Fund, 1986-1988 (Box 116)
  - Duke/Durham Fellows, 1986-1989 (Box 116)
  - Duke Endowment, 1986-1989 (Box 116)
  - Duke Endowment Leaves, 1982-1984 (Box 116)
  - Duke Futures, 1985-1989 (Box 116)
  - Duke Living History Committee, 1986 (Box 116)
  - Duke Magazine, 1987-1988 (Box 116)
  - Duke Press, 1986-1987 (Box 116)
  - Duke Preview Program, 1987-1989 (Box 117)
  - Early Identification Program, 1985 (Box 117)
  - Economics Department, 1985-1989 (Box 117)
  - Editors of Scholarly Journals, 1985 (Box 117)
  - Education, General, 1986 (Box 117)
  - Education, Program in, 1986-1989 (Box 117)
  - Education, Program in, 1985 (Box 118)
  - Educational Facilities Committee, 1986 (Box 118)
  - Edwards, Ben, 1987-1988 (Box 118)
  - Emeriti Space, 1986-1989 (Box 118)
  - Engineering, 1985-1989 (Box 118)
  - English Department, 1986-1989 (Box 118)
  - English Department, 1985 (Box 119)
  - Enrollment, 1987-1989 (Box 119)
  - Equipment, Furnishings and Renovations A and S, 1986 (Box 119)
  - Erasmus Club, 1980-1986 (Box 119)
  - Executive Vice President, 1988 (Box 119)
  - Faculty, General, 1985-1989 (Box 119)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1984-1988 (Box 119)
  - Faculty Honors, 1984-1985 (Box 119)
  - Faculty-in-Residence, 1983-1988 (Box 119)
  - Faculty Searches, 1988-1989 (Box 119)
  - Faculty Searches, 1984-1988 (Box 120)
  - Faculty Voting Privileges, ad hoc committee on, 1986-1987 (Box 120)
  - Fellowships, 1981-1989 (Box 120)
  - Film and Video, 1987-1988 (Box 120)
  - Financial Aid, 1987-1989 (Box 120)
  - Folger Institute, 1987-1988 (Box 120)
  - Forecast, Arts and Sciences, 1985-1986 (Box 120)
  - Foreign Language Institute, 1983-1986 (Box 120)
  - Forestry School, 1987-1989 (Box 120)
  - Founders' Day, 1987-1989 (Box 120)
  - Fraternities, 1985-1988 (Box 121)
  - Freshman Seminars, 1985-1989 (Box 121)
  - Friedl, Ernestine Endowment for the A and S, 1985 (Box 121)
  - Fritz London Project, 1987-1989 (Box 121)
  - Fulbright-Hayes Scholarship, 1985-1989 (Box 121)
  - Fuqua School of Business, 1985-1989 (Box 121)
  - Fuqua School of Business Development, 1986-1987 (Box 121)
  - Geography Proposal, 1988-1989 (Box 121)
  - Geology Department, 1985-1989 (Box 121)
  - Germanic Languages and Literature, Department of, 1988 (Box 121)
  - Germanic Languages and Literature, 1985-1987 (Box 122)
  - Gifts/Development, 1985-1989 (Box 122)
  - Glasgow Program, 1985 (Box 122)
  - Grades and Grade Changes, 1975-1986 (Box 122)
  - Graduate Awards, 1986-1988 (Box 122)
  - Graduate Education, Report on, 1987 (Box 122)
  - Graduate School, 1985-1989 (Box 122)
  - Graduate School Executive Committee, 1989 (Box 122)
  - Graduate School Executive Committee, 1985-1988 (Box 123)
  - Graduation Lists, 1985-1988 (Box 123)
  - Grounds Task Force Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 123)
  - GTE FOCUS Program, 1983-1987 (Box 123)
  - Guggenheim Fellowships, 1980-1987 (Box 123)
  - Handbooks, Departmental, 1985-1986 (Box 123)
  - Hariri Foundation, 1986 (Box 123)
  - Health, Physical Education and Recreation, 1986-1989 (Box 123)
  - Higher Education and National Affairs, 1980-1989 (Box 123)
  - History Department, 1985-1989 (Box 123)
  - History of Medicine, 1986 (Box 123)
  - History, Sociology and Philosophy of Science, 1985-1987 (Box 123)
  - Holmes Group, 1986-1989 (Box 123)
  - Honors, 1985-1987 (Box 123)
  - House Courses, 1974-1989 (Box 123)
  - Housing, 1983-1987 (Box 123)
  - Howard Foundation, George A. and Eliza Gardner, 1983-1986 (Box 123)
  - Human Development Program, Undergraduate Committee on, 1986-1989 (Box 124)
  - Human Resources, 1985-1989 (Box 124)
  - IBM, 1983-1987 (Box 124)
  - IBYCUS, Computer-Classical Studies, 1984-1987 (Box 124)
  - Immigration and Naturalization Services, 1989 (Box 124)
  - Incompletes, 1983 (Box 124)
  - Infirmary, 1984 (Box 124)
  - Information Systems, 1985-1989 (Box 124)
  - In-School Scholarship Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 124)
  - Institute of the Arts, 1987-1989 (Box 124)
  - Institute of the Arts, 1985-1986 (Box 125)
  - Institute of the Arts, Executive Committee on, 1980-1986 (Box 125)
  - International Studies, 1985-1989 (Box 125)
  - Internship Program, Undergraduate, 1985-1987 (Box 125)
  - Irregular Appointments, 1985-1986 (Box 125)
  - Islamic and Arabian Studies, 1987-1988 (Box 125)
  - Islamic and Arabian Studies, 1986 (Box 126)
  - James B. Duke Professorships, 1983-1984 (Box 126)
  - Johnson Foundation, Robert Wood, 1983 (Box 126)
  - Joint and Secondary Appointments, 1989 (Box 126)
  - Jones Foundation, Fletcher Ryan, 1983 (Box 126)
  - Judaic Studies, 1986-1988 (Box 126)
  - Judicial Board, 1986-1989 (Box 126)
  - Junior Faculty, 1985-1990 (Box 126)
  - Kaiser Family Foundation, Henry J., 1982 (Box 126)
  - Kaneb Endowment, 1983 (Box 126)
  - Laboratory Animals, 1984-1990 (Box 126)
  - Land Use Development, 1986-1989 (Box 126)
  - Language Institute, 1981-1985 (Box 126)
  - Language Laboratory, 1987-1988 (Box 126)
  - Law School, 1985-1988 (Box 126)
  - Leadership Program, 1985-1988 (Box 126)
  - Learning Disabilities, 1986-1988 (Box 126)
  - Leaves and Sabbaticals, 1983-1989 (Box 126)
  - Leaves, Junior Faculty, 1985-1987 (Box 126)
  - Library, 1985-1988 (Box 127)
  - Life Science Council, 1986 (Box 127)
  - Lingua Franca, 1989 (Box 127)
  - Linguistics, 1985-1989 (Box 127)
  - Literature, Graduate Program in, 1987-1988 (Box 127)
  - Literature, Program in, 1987-1988 (Box 127)
  - MacAnderson Scholarship Fund, 1976-1990 (Box 127)
  - Madagascar Exchanges, 1989 (Box 127)
  - Management Sciences, Undergraduate Courses, 1988-1989 (Box 127)
  - Marine Laboratory, 1985-1988 (Box 127)
  - Marine Laboratory Advisory Committee, 1987 (Box 127)
  - Marshall Scholarship Committee, 1980-1990 (Box 127)
  - Marxism and Society, 1981-1985 (Box 127)
  - Masters in the Arts of Liberal Studies, MALS, 1984-1989 (Box 127)
  - Masters in the Art of Teaching, MAT, 1986-1989 (Box 127)
  - Mathematical and Computation in Medicine, Center for, 1986 (Box 127)
  - Mathematical and Computational Biology, Center for, 1986-1988 (Box 127)
  - Mathematics, 1985-1989 (Box 128)
  - Medical Center, 1984-1989 (Box 128)
  - Medical Excuses, 1989 (Box 128)
  - Medieval and Renaissance Committee, 1984-1989 (Box 128)
  - Military Science, 1985-1989 (Box 128)
  - Minister to the University, 1980-1987 (Box 128)
  - Minority Affairs, 1987-1990 (Box 128)
  - Minority Affairs, 1985-1986 (Box 129)
  - Minority Student Science Counselor, 1984-1987 (Box 129)
  - Morocco at Duke Program, 1985-1989 (Box 129)
  - Murphy Center, Charles S., 1987 (Box 129)
  - Music Bequest, Carrabina, 1981-1983 (Box 129)
  - Music Department, 1985-1989 (Box 129)
  - Named Instructorships, 1979-1989 (Box 129)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1981-1989 (Box 129)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1984-1988 (Box 129)
  - NEH Challenge Grant, 1984-1989 (Box 129)
  - NEH Summer Stipend, 1989 (Box 129)
  - NEH Summer Stipend, 1983-1988 (Box 130)
  - NSF-Science Development and Undergraduate Teaching, 1985-1989 (Box 130)
  - NSF-Visiting Professorships for Women, 1983-1989 (Box 130)
  - Naval Science Department, 1985-1988 (Box 130)
  - Neurosciences, Undergraduate Program in, 1986-1988 (Box 130)
  - New Faculty, 1986-1988 (Box 130)
  - New Full-Time Faculty and Instructional Staff, 1985 (Box 130)
  - New York Arts Program, 1984-1987 (Box 130)
  - Noonan Proposal Experimental Education, 1987 (Box 130)
  - North Carolina Academy of Sciences, 1979-1986 (Box 130)
  - North Carolina Board of Science and Technology, 1987 (Box 130)
  - North Carolina School of Science and Mathematics, 1986-1989 (Box 130)
  - NSA/Duke Cooperative Agreement, 1985 (Box 130)
  - Opportunity Development, Office of, 1984-1986 (Box 130)
  - Orientation, 1985-1988 (Box 130)
  - Oxford Summer Program, 1984-1985 (Box 130)
  - Packard Scholarship, David and Lucile, 1988-1989 (Box 130)
  - Parents' Newsletter, 1984-1987 (Box 131)
  - Parents' Weekend, 1987-1989 (Box 131)
  - Part-time and Instructional Staff, Arts and Sciences, 1982-1988 (Box 131)
  - Performing Practice, Center for, 1987 (Box 131)
  - Performing Artists, Status of, 1984-1989 (Box 131)
  - Ph.D. Programs, 1983 (Box 131)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1976-1989 (Box 131)
  - Physical Science Council, 1986 (Box 131)
  - Philosophy Department, 1985-1988 (Box 131)
  - Physical Plant, 1974-1988 (Box 131)
  - Physics Department, 1985-1989 (Box 131)
  - Phytotron, 1980-1989 (Box 131)
  - Placement Services, 1986-1990 (Box 131)
  - Planning-General, 1983-1986 (Box 131)
  - Plant Science Center, 1987-1988 (Box 131)
  - Political Science Department, 1985-1989 (Box 132)
  - Pre-Business, 1985-1988 (Box 132)
  - Pre-Major Advising, 1985-1989 (Box 132)
  - President, 1985-1989 (Box 132)
  - Primate Center, 1987-1989 (Box 132)
  - Primate Center, 1986 (Box 133)
  - Private Adjudication Center, 1983 (Box 133)
  - Problems of Knowledge Faculty Seminar, 1985-1989 (Box 133)
  - Profiles of Departments and Programs, 1986-1987 (Box 133)
  - Promotion and Tenure Information, 1985-1989 (Box 133)
  - Provost, 1984-1989 (Box 133)
  - Provost Staff, 1986 (Box 133)
  - Psychology Department, Confidential, 1985-1986 (Box 133)
  - Psychology Department, 1989 (Box 133)
  - Psychology Department, 1985-1988 (Box 134)
  - Public Education and Training of Teachers, University Committee on, 1986-1989 (Box 134)
  - Public Policy Studies Department, 1985-1989 (Box 134)
  - Putman, Charles, Dean and Vice Provost for Reappointment and Development, 1989 (Box 134)
  - Putman, Charles, Dean and Vice Provost for Research and Development, 1986-1988 (Box 135)
  - Questionnaires and Surveys, 1987-1989 (Box 135)
  - Race Relations, 1984-1985 (Box 135)
  - Reappointments, Arts and Sciences, 1983-1987 (Box 135)
  - Registrar, 1984-1989 (Box 135)
  - Regulation Center, 1985-1986 (Box 135)
  - Religion Department, 1985-1989 (Box 135)
  - Research Assistantship Program, Undergraduate, 1985-1989 (Box 135)
  - Research Professors, 1984 (Box 135)
  - Research Support, 1988-1989 (Box 135)
  - Research Support, 1985-1987 (Box 136)
  - Research Triangle Park, 1987 (Box 136)
  - Residential Colleges, 1984-1987 (Box 136)
  - Residential Life, 1986-1989 (Box 136)
  - Residential Life, President's Committee on, 1984-1985 (Box 136)
  - Residential Life, Undergraduate Task Force Committee on, 1986 (Box 136)
  - Rhodes Scholarship Committee, 1975-1986 (Box 136)
  - Rochester, University of, 1988-1989 (Box 136)
  - Romance Studies Department, 1987-1989 (Box 136)
  - Romance Languages Department, 1985-1986 (Box 137)
  - Round Table, 1985-1986 (Box 137)
  - Salary Study, 1985 (Box 137)
  - Science Council, 1984-1985 (Box 137)
  - Science, Technology, and Human Values, 1986-1989 (Box 137)
  - Scheduling Committee, University, 1985-1989 (Box 137)
  - Scholarships and Fellowships, 1985-1989 (Box 137)
  - Scholarships, Four County Area, 1984-1987 (Box 137)
  - Search Committees, 1985-1986 (Box 137)
  - Searle Scholars Program, 1984-1986 (Box 137)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1985-1986 (Box 137)
  - Sigma Xi, Duke University Chapter, 1982-1989 (Box 137)
  - Signs, 1984-1989 (Box 137)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1985-1989 (Box 137)
  - Sloan Fellowships, 1985-1989 (Box 137)
  - Sociology Department, 1985-1989 (Box 137)
  - Space, Arts and Sciences, 1985-1988 (Box 137)
  - Spanish Studies, Center for, 1987 (Box 137)
  - Special Programs and Topics of Study, 1980-1982 (Box 137)
  - Statistics, 1984-1986 (Box 137)
  - Statistics and Decision Sciences, Institute for, 1985-1989 (Box 137)
  - Students' Academic Concerns, 1981 (Box 137)
  - Student Activities, 1983-1989 (Box 137)
  - Student Affairs, 1989 (Box 137)
  - Student Affairs, 1986-1988 (Box 138)
  - Student Affairs Trustee Committee, 1986 (Box 138)
  - Student Discrimination, 1982 (Box 138)
  - Student Life, 1986-1989 (Box 138)
  - Student Projects, 1983-1989 (Box 138)
  - Student Research, 1988 (Box 138)
  - Student Suggestions, 1988-1989 (Box 138)
  - Study Abroad General, 1986-1989 (Box 138)
  - Study Abroad Task Force, 1987 (Box 138)
  - STHV Course, 1988 (Box 138)
  - Summer Session, 1985-1989 (Box 138)
  - Summer Supplements/Faculty, 1982-1989 (Box 139)
  - Talent Identification Program, 1987-1989 (Box 139)
  - Teacher Course Evaluation, 1987-1989 (Box 139)
  - Teaching Analysis, 1989 (Box 139)
  - Teaching Loads, 1987-1989 (Box 139)
  - Technology and the Liberal Arts, 1986-1989 (Box 139)
  - Technology Center, 1986 (Box 139)
  - Telecommunications, 1987-1989 (Box 139)
  - Terry Sanford Lecturer, 1988-1989 (Box 139)
  - Transfer Students, 1984-1985 (Box 139)
  - Texas Instrument Foundation, 1983-1988 (Box 139)
  - Trent Memorial Foundation, Inc., Josiah Charles, 1987-1989 (Box 139)
  - Trent Memorial Foundation, Inc. Josiah Charles, 1985-1986 (Box 140)
  - Triangle Universities Nuclear Laboratories, TUNL, 1982-1988 (Box 140)
  - Trustees, 1986-1989 (Box 140)
  - Trustee Lists, 1987-1988 (Box 140)
  - Trinity College, 1983-1986 (Box 141)
  - Trinity College Distinguished Teaching Awards, 1984-1986 (Box 141)
  - Tropical Environmental Center, 1986 (Box 141)
  - Tuition, 1985-1987 (Box 141)
  - Tuition Charges, 1987-1989 (Box 141)
  - Tulane Site Visit, 1988 (Box 141)
  - Tutoring, 1985-1989 (Box 141)
  - Umbria Jazz, 1983-1987 (Box 141)
  - Undergraduate Affairs, Council on, 1989 (Box 141)
  - University Counsel, 1986-1988 (Box 141)
  - University Counsel and Exec. VP for Finance, Business and Law, 1984-1988 (Box 141)
  - University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, 1987-1988 (Box 141)
  - University Relations, 1987-1991 (Box 141)
  - University Secretary, 1984-1989 (Box 141)
  - University Union, 1985-1989 (Box 141)
  - Vertices, 1985 (Box 141)
  - Vienna Program, 1986-1988 (Box 141)
  - Visiting Scholars, 1987-1989 (Box 141)
  - Waterman, Alan T., Award, 1983-1988 (Box 141)
  - Washington University, 1.a. Study, 1987-1988 (Box 141)
  - Weller, Robert, 1987-1990 (Box 141)
  - White House Fellowships, 1989 (Box 141)
  - Women's Center UNC/Duke, 1987 (Box 141)
  - Women's Center UNC/Duke, 1985-1986 (Box 142)
  - Women Faculty, 1980-1988 (Box 142)
  - Women's Studies, 1985-1989 (Box 142)
  - Women's Studies, 1985 (Box 143)
  - Women's Studies Gender and Science, 1985-1986 (Box 143)
  - Writing Center, 1983-1986 (Box 143)
  - Writing Committee, Student, 1984-1985 (Box 143)
  - Writing Program, Advisory Committee on, 1987 (Box 143)
  - Writing Program, University, 1987-1989 (Box 143)
  - Writing Specialist, 1985-1986 (Box 143)
  - Zoology Department, 1985-1989 (Box 143)
  - Agreement between Duke University and the University of Paris, 1985 (Box 144)
  - NWAVE XVIII, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Graphic Design in Publishing, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Project Wild, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Migrants, Immigrants and Refugees, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Youth in Crisis, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Homelessness in NYC and Beyond, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Asians in America: Prospects for the Future, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Women and the Law, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Balancing Career and Relationships: Exploring Options for Life after Duke, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Balancing Career and Personal Relationships: Exploring Options for Life after Duke, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Perspectives on Africa, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Social Conflict in the South, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Houses Courses not Approved, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Soviet Seapower and Contemporary Naval Issues, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Political Thought and Social Activism, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Filmic Images of Liberation and Oppression, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Health and Medical Care in the U.S., 1988 (Box 144)
  - No Place to Go: The Homeless and Housing Crisis, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Women and the Law, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Contemporary Career Choices for Women in the Christian Church, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Masculinity and Beyond, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Scholarship and Publishing: Documenting a Feminist Perspective, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Magnitudes in a World with Nuclear Weapons, 1988 (Box 144)
  - Racial Stereotypes in American Political Culture: An Asian Paradigm, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Health and Power in North Carolina's Black Belt, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Looking Ahead for Change: Homelessness in America, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Current Problems of America's Youth and Youth Policy, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Cosmic Consciousness: A Comparative Study of Mystical Religious Systems, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Women in Black and White: Perspectives on Contemporary U.S. Society, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Body Image and Women: Understanding Ourselves within a Sociocultural Context, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Women and the Law, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Balancing Career and Personal Relationships: Exploring Options for Life After Duke, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Filmic Images of Individualism, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Experiential Education: Project Wild, 1989 (Box 144)
  - House Course Approved but Canceled, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Adlai Stevenson and the Modern Democratic Party, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Advanced Political Thought and Social Activism, 1989 (Box 144)
  - List of House Courses, Fall 1989 (Box 144)
  - The World of the New Testament, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Practical Responses to Issues of Social Conscience, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Current Issues in Catholicism, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Towards an Ecological Society, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Developing the Self Mind and Voice: Women's Ways of Knowing, 1989 (Box 144)
  - International Perspective on Female Psychology and Sexuality, 1989 (Box 144)
  - Freedom and Constraint: The Role of Censorship in a Free Society, 1989 (Box 144)
  - List of House Courses, Spring 1989 (Box 144)
  - House Courses: Publicity up thru 1988 (Box 144)
  - Jewish-Christian Relations, 1990 (Box 144)
  - The Nature of the University, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Doin' Theory: Critical Thought through the Literary Model, 1990 (Box 144)
  - The Ethnic Experience in America, 1990 (Box 144)
  - House Course Approved but Canceled, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Project Wild, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Exploring the Catholic Faith, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Two Peoples, One Land: Palestinian and Jewish Nationalism, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Issues of Human Sex and Sexuality in the Arts, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Migrant Farmworker Children, Education and Documentary Studies, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Indigent Health Care in the United States, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Youth in Crisis, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Educating At-Risk Students, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Power Struggles and Health in North Carolina's Black Belt, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Homelessness in America, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Balancing Career and Personal Relationships: Exploring Options for Life after Duke, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Women's Writing and the Publishing Enterprises: A Feminine Perspective, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Exploring Reproductive Rights and Choices, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Women and the Law, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Men and Gender Issues: A Course for Men about Challenges of Today and Prospects for the Future, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Thinking about Ourselves: Surviving as Black Women in Today's Society (Box 144)
  - Escaping Ecocidal Culture: Student Explorations of Ecological Lifestyles, Careers, and Social Change, 1990 (Box 144)
  - The Philosophy of Psychology, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Freud, 1990 (Box 144)
  - The World of the New Testament, 1990 (Box 144)
  - House Course Approved but Canceled, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Catholic Faith, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Practical Responses to Issues of Community Leadership Development, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Women and Leadership, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Women and the Law, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Men and Gender Issues, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Intro to the Deaf World: Bond between ASL and Deaf Culture, 1990 (Box 144)
  - Multiple Personality and Demonological Possession, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Honduras: Towards Understanding, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Traditions in Dialogue, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Child Care: The Issue of the Nineties, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Project Wild, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Identity and Growth: A Poetry Writing Workshop, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Presbyterian Perspectives: Past and Present, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Museum Education: History, Theory, Practice, 1991 (Box 145)
  - A Cross-Cultural Study of Blacks in the Diaspora, 1991 (Box 145)
  - An Introduction to ASL and the Deaf Culture, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Migrant Farmworkers in North Carolina, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Cooperative Living for a Better Environment, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Educating At-Risk Students, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Homelessness in NYC, 1991 (Box 145)
  - House Course Approved but Canceled, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Indigent Health Care in the US, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Youth in Crisis, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Men and Gender Issues, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Singing for their Lives: A Case Study of the Women's Music Movement, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Balancing Career and Personal Relationships: Exploring Options for Life after Duke, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Whose Health is It Anyway: Women and Health Care from a Feminist Perspective, 1991 (Box 145)
  - Women and the Law, 1991 (Box 145)